eventective.com 2006-06-20

# Privacy Policy for Eventective

Eventective.com ("Website") is strongly committed to your right to privacy and to taking steps designed to secure your personal and financial information. To earn your trust and confidence in our commitment, the intent of this policy is to fully disclose our privacy practices to you. We will only use your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

The Eventective.com website is owned and operated by Eventective, Inc., which is located at 480 Congress Street, Portland, ME 04101. The website refers visitors to hotels, restaurants, and other facilities that have meeting and event rooms, as well as to event- and meeting-related service providers.

In some instances, when you provide personal information to this website, you are providing it to both Eventective.com and to one of the companies featured on the site. For example, if you create an account with Eventective.com and then search for a facility in which to hold your event, you may request that information about your event be sent to certain facilities. In this case, your information will be provided to both Eventective.com and the facilities you have chosen.

Consequently, to understand how any information collected may be used, you should review both Eventective.com's privacy policy and the privacy policy of the hotel, facility, or service provider you intend to work with or request information from.

We encourage you to read the Eventective.com privacy policy, as well as those of our participating facilities and service providers, so that you understand what types of personal information are collected and how this information may be used. 

**As part of our Privacy Policy, we address the following:**

* The personal information we collect   

* With whom your information is shared and how it is used   

* The choices you have about the collection and use of your information   

* The security measures we take to protect your personal information   

* Additional information about online privacy and changes to our policy 

**The personal information we collect**  
Eventective.com and its partners collect personal information necessary to respond to your requests for information about facilities, events, and service providers, as well as our customized products and services, and to allow you to use the resources available on our website, including the creation and maintenance of an account. Personal information includes, but is not limited to, name, physical address, email address, phone number, age and any other information that itself identifies or, when tied to the above information, may identify you as a specific individual. Eventective.com and its partners also collect information related to your event, including dates and locations of your event, and information relating to the number of attendees. Eventective.com also uses order forms for you to request certain information, products and services. On such order forms, we collect your contact information, financial information (including credit card numbers) and demographic information. 

**Referral Program and Surveys.** Eventective.com offers a Referral Program that rewards you for referring other users and members. Your participation in this Referral Program is entirely optional. Information we collect for the Referral Program can include your contact information as well as the contact information of those you refer. Eventective.com also values the opinions and comments from all of our users, so we frequently conduct surveys online, via email, or by telephone. Your participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Information we collect in online surveys will include general information on the use of our site and other demographic information, such as age and income bracket. Survey participants are anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey. 

**Cookies.** "Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies in several very common ways. Cookie files are used to better understand how you go through our website so that we may tailor your experience at our website. Cookies are also used to tell us whether you have visited our website previously, and to help us determine whether you came to our website from a particular Internet link, banner advertisement, or search engine. Cookies can also be used to help you to save and retrieve passwords and other information and preferences you use on our website, saving you from having to re-enter this information upon every visit to our website. Cookies cannot and will not be used by us to retrieve any personal information about you from your computer that you have not previously and voluntarily provided to us. However, cookies may also be received when you link to our partners' sites or when you view or click on banner advertisements served by our outside advertising company and we do not have control over how they use this information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block them in the future. However, most of our features will not function if you do not accept cookies. 

**IP Addresses.** When you connect to our website, we record your IP addresses and information on the type of operating system (ex. Windows 98) and browser software (ex. Microsoft Internet Explorer) you are using. This helps us to diagnose problems with our servers and for system administration. Your IP address is also used to help gather aggregated demographic information. 

**Forums, message boards, and chat rooms.** We may make forums, message boards, and chat rooms available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**With whom your information is shared and how it is used**  
When you provide information to Eventective.com, the information is stored in our database. Such information is used by Eventective.com in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Information we collect is used to tailor your experience at our site (including the creation of an online event planning tool), to show you content that we think you might be interested in, and to display the content according to your preferences. We also use such personal information to send you promotional materials on us and some of our partners. Your contact information may also be used if it becomes necessary to contact you. 

When you use a credit card to purchase goods and services through our website, your encrypted credit card information will be sent to our retail partners that provide registry and shopping services or to Authorize.net (an online credit card payment processor used by many websites) to authorize your payment. Although this Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices or policies of any such other entities, we intend to require that all of our partners agree not to use your personal information, except as fully disclosed to you or authorized by you. 

Any information we collect may be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. In addition, we may from time to time hire a third party to act on our behalf for projects such as market research surveys and contest entry processing, and we will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. Survey and contest participation is entirely optional. The information we provide to such third parties will be protected by a confidentiality agreement that will obligate the third party to use such information solely to complete the specific project. 

In addition to the circumstances described above, we may disclose your information if required to do so by law, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authorities, or in the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable, including (without limitation) when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. 

**The choices you have about the collection and use of your information**  
As a user or customer, you will occasionally receive email updates from us about important functionality changes, special offers from us and our partners, new Eventective.com services and other noteworthy news items about us and our partners. We hope you will find these updates interesting and informative. Of course, if you would rather not receive them, just let us know by clicking on the opt-out link at the bottom of the email or let our partners know by following their instructions. If you have provided the name and email address of another event participant, Eventective.com will send such participant an email inviting him or her to visit our site and giving such participant the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future information regarding Eventective.com and its partners. Our site also provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving such communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information from you. In other words, if you don't want us or our partners to send you emails about our or their business, just let us know. Eventective.com reserves the right to limit registration to those who will accept emails and to those who will provide the requested information. 

Eventective.com provides you with the ability to receive email subscriptions to various services we provide. If you elect to receive such email subscriptions, you can opt-out of receiving future emails by following the opt-out instructions on the bottom of every email you receive.

**The security measures we take to protect your personal information**  
All order information you provide to us and all information contained in your online account is transmitted using SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. SSL is a widely used coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt or scramble data before you send it to us. Transactions will not be permitted if your browser does not accept SSL encryption. Only authorized personnel from Eventective.com or its partners can decode this information and such personnel will only do so in accordance with our or their Privacy Policy. In addition, Eventective.com does not store any of your credit card information. All of that information is stored with our credit card processor, Authorize.net, in accordance with their privacy policy.   
In addition, when you register for certain online features, you will have the opportunity to select whether you wish to make your event information available to your other event participants via a password. If you do not elect to make your event information available only via password, anyone visiting our website will be able to search for your event by using first and/or last names and dates (and on some pages, city or state). 

**Additional information about online privacy and changes to our policy**  
Please be aware that on our site we have advertisements and links to other websites that may collect personal information about you. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices or policies of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all such sites, as their policies may be materially different from our Privacy Policy. Any material changes in the way we use personal information will be described in future versions of this Privacy Policy. If you have any concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please contact Eventective at the address below. We will attempt to respond to all reasonable concerns or inquiries as quickly as possible. 

Our address  
Eventective, Inc.  
480 Congress Street  
Portland, ME 04101  
http://www.eventective.com
